Sombra online
isn't it a little embarrassing to get
beaten up by a monkey have you ever been
hit by a giant genetically engineered
gorilla
could arrange it for you
I can't stand you hackers you give those
of us with skill a bad name you know
that isn't the kind of hacking I do
right
you wouldn't believe what I learned
about you Sparrow I am at peace with who
I was your threat does not concern me
pleasure working with you Macri if that
is your real name don't know what you
heard my name's not Joe
let's remember that
what's the plan today Gabe you don't
mind if I call you Gabe do you stick to
the mission try to stick to the plan
Sombra look someone has to be ready when
all your careful planning doesn't pan
out so what are we doing here boss I
need to pay a visit to a friend
ah my favorite spider I wonder what sort
of web you're spinning now it'd be a
shame if something happened to you in
our next mission a real pity
don't think I don't recognize that
device of yours I know you stole it how
can I say a girl just has to have the
latest tech sometimes I feel a little
sick after using my translocator I'm
sure you know what I mean tracer what be
a problem if you just disappear forever
your friend Katya volts kya what will
you say when you learn the truth she's a
hero to all Russians I do not care what
you have to say
hi sorry Gabe
dorita